A Guide to the Records of the Division of Outreach and International Affairs, Sahel Regional Financial Management Project, 1982-1986
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Publications
  - Reports and Pubs; Cours de Compatbilite Generale: Plan Ocam (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Reports and Pubs; A Practical Manual for a Simplified Accounting System (Portuguese) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Reports and Pubs; Preparing, Evaluating, and Managing Development Projects (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Reports and Pubs; Project Analysis: Towards and Integrated Methodology (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Reports and Pubs; Promising Approaches to Project Management Improvement - Solomon (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Reports and Pubs; Public Administration in Africa: The Legacy of Inherited Colonial Institutions (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Reports and Pubs; Public Auditing Techniques for Performance Improvement (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Reports and Pubs; SRFMP Assessment Process and Workshop: An Overview (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Sahel Development Program" Annual Report to the Congress, 1982-02 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Sahel Program Management Assessment" (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Reports and Pubs; "SRFMP Accounting Manual for a Double Entry Accounting System" by Christian (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Budget
  - Budget; Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Budget; Inventory (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Budget; Gambia Inventory (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Budget; Senegal Inventory (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Budget; Chad Inventory (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Budget; Mali Inventory (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Budget; Niger Inventory (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Budget; Burkina Faso Inventory (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Budget; Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Budget; Shipping Export License (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Budget; Accounting (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Budget; Purchasing - Policy (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Budget; Financial Reports (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Budget; Old Financial Reports (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Budget; Financial Reports - Project Accounting System (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Budget; Travel Expenses (Box 25, Folder 16)